This is a short animation about empty bike docks.
It started as a dashboard.
Today I want to show you two new artifact types,
Claude Dashboards and Claude Motion.
Pretend that I run the operations team at a bike share.
Every weekday, the docks on the hill are empty by 8:15.
We need to get to the bottom of it.
We let Claude pull a year of ride data from our data warehouse
and lay it out as a nice dashboard.
As we look at the dashboard, a story takes shape.
And we'll need to tell this story to the whole team at our next all-hands meeting
to get them on board.
So we asked Claude to turn this dashboard into an animation,
using Claude Motion.
Claude turns it into an animated narrative.
Claude usually does a pretty good job right away,
but I can continue to tweak it and steer it with comments if I want to,
right there on the video.
I can send it to colleagues and they can comment too.
We can build the story together.
And if the team wants to take it further, we can export it straight into their design tools.
So that's Claude Dashboards and Claude Motion,
and you can try them out today.